hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is jeremi
Kowski and in this podcast I talk about
how to grow your coaching business if
you're an online Co coach course creator
or mentor and you want to scale to make
six and seven figures I've been doing
this for 21 years and I want to help you
get results now in this podcast episode
I want to talk about some of the changes
that have been happening in funnels and
marketing and a lot of some of the
things that I'm seeing that's that's
going on um AI has caused people's
attention span to go to zero and that
you know Tik Tok was doing the same
thing for a while we called the tiktock
ification of the internet now people
don't seem to even have the attention
span to sit through 3day 5day challenges
as far as that goes uh webinars depends
on what your Market is I guess what that
would be um but really like people want
quick answers they want to know right
away if they can take action and they're
willing to take action in the longer
term uh if they there is certainty as
far as that goes so we're shifting up
all of our funnels as far as this goes
um to you you almost have to as a
necessity feed into this as far as that
goes and so where I'm looking at the
shift is right now like my YouTube
videos anytime I post a long form video
on YouTube it's getting at least 100
views plus um and and and what I'm
including in those is a lot of the stuff
that I was talking about in my webinars
um a lot of the stuff on the podcast as
well because people want instant
gratification immediate uh information
as far as that goes now here's one of
the number one things that you have to
do you have to stay consistent as far as
the topics that you're promoting that
are related to selling the actual thing
that you sell one of the biggest
mistakes that we make is trying to get
engagement likes comments shares stuff
like that the engagement that you want
is
views views and time on platform now
more than ever whether it be how long
Somebody's Watching through an Instagram
reel how long Somebody's Watching
through a long form YouTube video how
long Somebody's Watching through a
webinar is important and there's a
process in delivering information that
actually keeps people hooked
longer watching and listening longer in
your content and so that's important to
honor that that's important to show up
with that in mind when you're creating
content when we're promoting our
business but here's where AI has to come
in and caused us a little bit of a of a
challenge that now I'm like okay great
let's adjust as far as this goes I can I
can see the writing on the wall as far
as this goes because you can type in
questions and get answers so quickly
everybody wants instant gratification
now they're willing to sit through um
you know a 30 minute training of some
kind maybe a 20 to 40 minute training if
it's really really good uh but beyond
that Beyond about 20 to 30 minutes if
they don't know who you are uh it's just
too long for a lot of people in the
initial touch Point as far as that goes
so what I'm shifting to is all my lead
magnets now I'm going you're going to
notice I'm going to do this is I'm going
to have lead magnets where I'm going to
have maybe four or five I'm going to
take all the webinars that I was
doing and and this is this is what I'm
planning on doing and y'all are
literally going to see me build this in
public as far as that goes uh if you're
a part of just following me and and
doing this and I got this from funnel
hacking a number of different funnels
and looking at what is everybody else
doing that's running a lot of ads for
the last 6 months by the way I'm going
to pause here that's an incredible thing
that you want to do you want to look at
what are your competitors doing what
formats are they actually marketing and
promoting for the last 6 to 12 months
this has been a massive shift in the
market as far as that goes now we're not
eliminating webinars or challenges but
we're creating vehicles to build trust
before those as far as that goes so the
idea is I think I can generate a ton
more leads to my email list that are
highly qualified highly nurtured um by
walking them through a very Punchy
packed 30-minute training now one of the
biggest things that we have to shift
away from is overe explaining things
okay so be willing to be Mis
misunderstood uh if you know that you're
talking just you got to assume that
you're talking to your buyers as far as
that goes you got to assume that you're
talking to people that understand what
you're talking about you got to speak
their language of course but you don't
want to overe explain like you're
talking to Outsiders trying to explain
to them what's going on and that was a
big mistake that I spent a lot of time
in my content and my training doing is I
was trying to bring Outsiders into my
world as far as that goes and they were
just like spinning their heads in
circles trying to make heads or tails of
all the stuff that I was saying and so
now I don't overe explain a lot of stuff
I I straight to the point of what I'm
trying to say and if you misunderstand
me I trust that you can be an adult and
ask a question you know or you're just
going to not follow me anymore because
you're just like okay well that's not
for me and so what happens is because
we're so pointed in what we're talking
about and we're not I'm not self-editing
as much I'm not considering all the
different ways that people might
misunderstand me or things like that as
I'm talking in a conversation I'm able
to actually get a lot more content out
faster I'm able to talk more like I do
with my higher level clients at a
smaller level now here's what I found
from this two things number one I've had
a lot of drop off from people that have
followed me for years have want nothing
to do with me right now and it's because
I've changed they don't like the vibe
that I put off they don't like how I'm
communicating uh but I've also had an
increase in the ones who really really
are a good Target fit for me in their
results that they've been getting and
the deeper connection that I've been
making with them and that is a win-win
winwin on massive scale for me to see
that as far as that goes I'm always
wanting to get a a lot of connection
with the best highest quality group
people that's going to get the most
amount of results everybody else I'm
willing to let them drop off especially
if they've been wasting my time and
theirs for that long you know and and
and they can come up with all the
different reasons why I'm not a good fit
for them I do not concern myself with
that because I'm willing to let them go
because we're pulling in a whole brand
new group of people we're pulling in an
elite group of people we're pulling in a
higher level of people as far as that
goes who can communicate on a higher
level because that's how that's how I'm
talking and that's how I'm communicating
from now on and so from this what you
have to do is you have to really
um understand specifically who you're
looking to reach you have to understand
how you help people what is your
expertise that you're going to bring to
the table what are your
superpowers as far as that goes and then
build something around those superpowers
in your offers in your lead magnets
everything needs to be actually drew the
diagram right here even your free stuff
to your paid stuff needs to be a
straight shot beline to whatever it is
that you are selling they need to be
nearly exactly the same thing but the
free stuff uh um is the initial starting
stages of it the paid stuff is what
they're actually paying for for the
implementation again if you don't
understand that side of it we're going
over that on my on my webinar this week
I am hosting a webinar on June 5th where
I'm going to be explaining a lot of that
how to build out your offers and stuff
like that there's some Nuance to it but
I want to I want to keep the new wants
much simpler moving forward um because
it doesn't have to be over complicated
so I'm so I'm looking at uh people who
they want to run really good Facebook
ads that's what we're going to be
focusing a lot of our marketing to a lot
of our marketing towards uh and and to
run a good Facebook ad you have to have
a good lead magnet you have to have a
good offer we're going to focus on
helping people build out their lead
magnets we're focusing on helping people
uh identify their Niche we're focusing
on helping people structure their
coaching programs these are all these
kind of beginning stages of marketing
building and creating a coaching program
and then how do we launch a group
program how do we
fulfill group coaching that does well
and if I can Encompass all of that trust
me if you start doing that you're going
to make six figures
okay if I can Encompass that showing
people how to go from zero finding their
Niche to Growing clients to making six
figures that is going to that's going to
scale to the to the Moon which is
awesome and so now I've gotten that like
really really dialed in we we we're
dialed in more now as far as our Niche
goes more now than ever we're going to
really be focusing in on on helping
people build out recurring Revenue
membership sites stuff so they can move
out of their corporate job and one piece
that I'm adding into it is helping
people they might be overwhelmed because
they're working a job or they have a lot
of stuff that they're doing outside of
what they're doing one of the things
that I've mastered literally mastered is
how I have very little time to build my
business and yet I show up at a high
level uh with with minimal amount of
time that I'm actually doing the
business work or even brainstorming in
my business because I'm spending time
doing other things as far as that goes
and this is something a I've learned
over the years uh but it doesn't have to
take you 21 years to get there I think
it's a it's a mental game is what that
is that side of it's a complete mental
game so all that to say I'm going to be
building out these short form lead
magnets that are like 20 to 30 minute
videos where I'm going to teach powerp
packed topics as far as this goes and
then from there I'll probably invite
people to webinars that I will host and
these might even be pre-recorded
webinars and then I'm and then I'll host
paid Events off of this so we're going
to have paid events where I'm live
everything else if it's free is all
going to be pre-recorded and automated
so that's going to be a whole brand new
kind of thing as well that I'm shifting
into so that I can remove myself having
to work on that I can record a
pre-recorded webinar I mean right now
it's 10:00 at night had some incredible
inspiration for this podcast right now
press record boom how did I get the
inspiration you might wonder I was
washing dishes watching a new show on uh
Netflix just I was washing dishes
watching a new show on Netflix Bing idea
for the podcast walked into my office
pressed record and that's how we started
this episode and that's literally the
amount of time that I spent brain brain
storming over this because I've
structured that activity to help me come
up with content and so that's a big part
of again what I teach a lot of people in
my mentorship program is how to not
spend a ton of time coming up with ideas
for your content relaxing yourself way
much not worrying so much about saying
everything perfectly sounding perfect
doing all the perfect stuff looking and
appearing like you got it all figured
out all of that is a facade it is and
it's not reality and it's not going to
make you a dime more of money as far as
it goes in fact in my experience it will
make you lose money to operate in that
way anytime I try to operate in that way
I lose money because I'm not being
authentic I'm trying to be like what I
think people want when I can show up
authentically and I've actually aligned
the professional identity of my business
to how I am authentically and now
they're integrated as the same thing
which is awesome that's why you're
seeing a new Cadence to how I'm
talking had to work through some therapy
stuff over the last 2 and 1 half years
to even get there that's why even if you
listen to some of my older podcasts
different confidence level different
tone of voice even as far as it goes
it's not that I'm actually like changing
who I am as far as it goes I'm really
becoming the ultimate version that I'm
creating of myself and that's one of the
biggest things is I'm
crafting Jeremiah Kowski
this this this who I am in my life to be
everything that I've always wanted and
dreamed of and so that's how I get to
show up it's it's a Jeremiah Kowski that
brings in Maximum cash flow shows up at
the highest level for his family is
important and and produces the best
results for my clients and I would say
that those are like if I'm looking at my
life right now those are the three top
priorities for me
crushing it with the family it's number
one crushing it for my paid clients
that's number two and then just being an
expert bomb.com
incredible at sales and marketing at the
highest level content creator uh teacher
speaker um somebody that people actually
want to listen to the stuff that I want
to say and and I can tell you a couple
years ago that wasn't me I couldn't show
up that way I couldn't talk that way I
couldn't communicate that
way and and and I know 2 years from now
I'm going to look back at this and be
like wow like that's Amateur hour right
there two and a half years ago was
Amateur hour for me and now I'm showing
up at I think the the highest level I
ever have um and it's amazing and so
that's just again like a kind of a
personal note for me but I say all that
to encourage you that you can get there
as well which is incredible you know
I've been in this industry for 21 years
but I I was never the guy in front of
the camera camera as much I and I was
always not being like fully myself now I
can say I'm I'm 100% being myself in all
the communications that I'm
having this is where being integrated
comes into play as far as that goes okay
but I digress from this what we're going
to be doing
is um lead magnets short form content
we're going to use all the same topics
that I've been doing because I've been
running a ton of webinars over the last
year and a half Russell Brunson says
this you got to run webinars for at
least a year to really dial in what
exactly you're going to do now I'm like
I'm so locked in as far as the topic
that people want to hear from me like
I've literally in the last week had so
many people reach out to want to coach
with me uh in my program that um you
know I'm considering moving away from
using a waiting list uh on my
accelerator right now we still have a
waiting list um but I'm considering
moving away from that because I think
we've gotten so locked in now as far as
what we're doing that it might not
benefit us as much by the way this is
one another key element I want to tell
you and I want to pause here one of the
biggest mistakes that we can make is you
can look at okay what does a millionaire
do what do somebody who's making seven
figures in their business do and then
you want to model what they're doing
that's a mistake in the fact that you
actually want to model what they did
from where you are at to what got them
there so if you're doing exactly what
I'm doing in my business and you're not
making six figures yet it's probably not
going to work for you as well but if you
did what got me from zero to six
figures which is what I teach you that's
going to get you there very quickly as
far as that goes you might say well why
wouldn't I just do it what you're doing
at seven figures here's why because
there was a process that got me here and
there's certain steps you can Skip and I
talk about how to accelerate those
timelines absolutely but there's some
data as well that you want that gets you
to the place where you want to be as far
as that goes understanding people
growing in your skill set becoming a
great communicator that takes time of
actually putting in the Reps it's like
working it's like an Olympic Athlete
showing up at that high level and so one
of the biggest problems people have is
they're so impatient they want the
results right away when in fact there is
a process to it and if you follow me if
you plug in with me if you listen to my
podcast if you listen to my content I
will give you that blueprint I will give
you exactly what the steps are to take
you can trust that every single time
okay so we got to keep it simple we got
to honor the fact that people's
attention span is much lower and we have
to honor the fact that they're now more
than ever the algorithms are really
really highly
addictive on social media and so if
you're marketing on social media you
have to tap right into that and be an
extension of that same addictive
algorithm and this might sound a little
bit uncomfortable because you're like
wait a sec I don't want to be like these
addictive algorithms you have to
literally teach your content in a way
that's a direct extension of all the
other content that they're seeing on the
algorithm meaning that it feels exactly
like the stuff that they're wanting to
engage with your Target
customer and you might watch the stuff
that your target clients engage with and
it does not feel like you or authentic
as far as that goes so that's where
there is a structure to how you want to
learn to communicate you want to model
what a lot of your competitors are doing
as far as their Cadence goes as far as
their tonality their tone of voice voice
um maybe even some of the words that
they're using um and you want to also
learn how to build excitement you want
to build uh anticipation you want to
build connection engagement where people
want to watch all the way to the end
because they're hanging on what you're
saying so this is exactly the same
structure that filmmakers take this is
exactly the same structure that
novelists take and video game creators
take and now it's coming into our social
media world where it's like okay and
it's always kind of been this way but
this is really the piece that you have
to get is you have to really tap into
there's certain triggers that fire off
dopamine in people's minds and it
creates this kind of dopamine drip in
their brains where it's like very um
exciting to listen to you it fires off
the triggers in the brains where it's
like the brain is like this is what I
want more of type of a thing and so it's
sticky and they get more hooked on it
and so what you got to do is you got to
create very sticky um highly you're
going to hook them in with your content
you're an extension of what these
addictive platforms do and the idea is
you because you're a coach and Mentor
you're moving people to your platform to
where if you're a good coach you're
going to you're actually going to help
people understand how digital detox is
helpful this is something I help people
with understanding how how looking at
like just being so sucked into the
algorithms is like literally rewiring
your brain in a way that's that's
against creating wealth and then you're
going to help people wire their brains
to understand to rise above the Matrix
as far as that goes is a big part of it
okay but you have to when you're
marketing when you're doing your sales
and marketing you have to go right into
the Matrix and actually communicate in
the same way that people expect on the
algorithms and this is where like if if
you're if you're our pride and ego could
get in the way of this or we're like
that well that's just not me I'm not
going to do that you know I'm I'm you
know I again I had I dealt with this
myself and now I've had to and and
that's one of the subtle shifts as well
in the content that I'm creating is is
that I that's part of why I don't over
over I'm not ere explaining everything
anymore is
because that creates much more engaging
content because it actually triggers
curiosity to create more
questions you want your content to
actually trigger curiosity as far as it
goes you want to become a great
communicator you want to learn how to
communicate in a way that people
actually want to listen to people
actually want to sit down and spend time
listening to and they and they and they
want more of what you're talking about I
hope I hope that when you're listening
to me like you want more of what I'm
talking about you want to learn more
about this this stuff you want to learn
more how you can make six figures in a
business using these Concepts you want
to learn more about how you can
make this kind of money working only 10
to 15 hours a week
even okay so again that's exactly what
we go over in my events it's exactly
what we help you with in my client
growth accelerator program if you're not
in the accelerator program would highly
encourage you to get on the waiting list
for it to jump in when we do open the
doors to it and become a client and to
work with us in there to help you build
out your landing pages to build out your
offers build your ads get the results
you want all right so hopefully this has
helped you it's giv you kind of a little
bit of a bird's eyee view as far as
where the landscape of things is headed
I've been talking about this the
ticktock ification of the internet for a
long time um it really is now it's AI is
the biggest is the biggest thing is
because it's because people want instant
gratification so you got to feed that
Beast you got to feed the instant
gratification drive that people have as
much as possible possible in the sales
process and then you you sort of like
get people off of that instant
gratification in a way that you're still
sort of feeding it that's why your your
courses and your coaching programs need
to have step by step you need to
provide uh like support and
accountability and this provides people
with a combination of everything that
they've always hoped and dreamed of that
keeps them hooked and sticky inside of
your ecosystem inside of your coaching
program the classes the courses the
information that they're able to get as
well keeps people engaged at those
levels all right so hopefully this has
helped you um I this is something I've
just been I've been tossing around
different ideas on I'm I'm going to be
refining it even more as far as this
goes moving forward I've been teaching a
lot of this to my coaching group I'm
going to start teaching more of it on
this podcast as well um it took me like
6 hours to explain what I just told you
in like 20 minutes 3 months ago go by
the way that's another skill set you
learn how to literally say the same
thing in a fraction of the amount of
time to pack a lot of punch I probably
could talk for another 20 more minutes
on this to dive deeper into the whole
like dopamine triggering process if you
understand how algorithms work and how
films and TV and video games and and
even fiction novels and even even
non-fiction now has to do this
nonfiction now just merely providing
good information is not good enough you
have to educate and
entertain and be
interesting it's not enough to just be
academic anymore you have to be
something that people really want to
spend more time consuming as far as that
goes and kind of and and and you can
craft all the highest quality education
and information in a highly engaging
entertaining way and so that's what
produces results that's what you're
looking for all right listen if this
podcast episode has helped you share it
with somebody make sure you subscribe
subscribe to the YouTube channel keep
plugging in I'd love to see you in our
in our coaching group all right talk
soon
[Music]
[Applause]